

# Luis Eduardo Urdaneta Martucci

Frontend Web Developer

LuisEUM95@gmail.com

+34 611 13 20 50



www.linkedin.com/in/luiseum



@LuisEUM



https://github.com/LuisEUM



https://alkitu.com

#### SUMMARY

Web developer, graphic designer, and digital marketing specialist with more than 2 years of experience in each field. I founded a freelancer business during the quarantine where I led teams on more than 15 large projects in France, Spain, USA, and Morocco. I make businesses and projects reach their full growth potential with my multidisciplinary skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

Sep. 2022 - Present

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya - Spain Digital Interaction and Multimedia Techniques Degree

Apr. 2022 - Oct. 2022 IronHack - Spain Web Development FullStack

Intensive Bootcamp to learn the full MERN stack.

Sep. 2012 - Mar. 2017

Universidad Simón Bolívar - Venezuela Bachelor's Degree in International Bussiness

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Sept. 2016

Outstanding Note - Internship Evaluation Report

In the business internship defense, the jury can assign an outstanding grade for a score of 4.75 out of 5. I achieved the maximum scale of 5 in my defense and get awarded the honorable mention.

#### SKILLS

- MongoDB
- Express JS
- React JS Node JS
- ISX
- NextJS
- **TailwindCSS**
- Framer Motion
- **ESlint**
- Puppeteer
- Postman
- Javascript (ES6)
- HTML5 CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Handlebars .
- RESTful APIs

- GitHub
- WordPress
- SFO
- SEM
- Google Ads
- Google Tag Manager
- Google Search Console
- Google Analytics
- UX/ŬI
- Figma
- Adobe Photoshops
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Indesign
- Adobe After Effects
- Microsft office
- Social Media

## LANGUAGES

- Spanish Native
- English Fluent
- Italian Beginner
- French Beginner

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Tangle - Netherlands

Nov. 2022 - Feb. 2023

**Web Developer** 

Tangle Offline Website: https://tangle-offline-website.vercel.app Repository: https://github.com/LuisEUM/tangle-offline-website Techs: NextJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion, and ESlint.

InstagramScraper - API RESTful

Repository: https://github.com/LuisEUM/InstagramScraper

Techs: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, Puppeteer, and Postman

#### Bootcamp Ironhack - Spain

Apr. 2022 - Oct. 2022

**Web Developer** 

Gousty The Ghost - Desktop Game: https://alkitu.com/gousty Repository: https://github.com/LuisEUM/Gousty\_the\_ghost Techs: CSS3, HTML5, and JavaScript (ES6)

BIG MENU - Menu creator: https://menuproject-production.up.railway.app Repository: https://github.com/theBigMenu/menuProject Techs: MongoDB, ExpressJS, NodeJS, Handlebars, and Bootstrap

Top Top - Restaurant Network: https://toprestaurant-production.up.railway.app Repository: https://github.com/LuisEUM/TopRestaurant Techs: MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS, Bootstrap, and Framer Motion

#### Alkitu - Spain

Mar. 2020 - Present

#### Freelancer and Founder

Designed and developed brands, webs, and advertising material. Improved companies with digital marketing strategies, and led a team of freelancers serving over 30 clients from different countries.

#### Jan. 2019 - Dec. 2021 La Plataforma Publicitaria - Spain Administrative Assistant/Graphic Designer

Analyzed, prepared, and designed the brands, digital advertising material, and printing material of more than 200 clients.

#### OcasionPlus, S. L. - Spain

Jan. 2019 - Nov. 2021

#### Administrative Assistant/Photographer

Teamed with another photographer and took pictures, edited, and published over 1.000 cars in 3 different stores in Valencia.

## L'etiquette eventos - Ecuador

Jun. 2017 - Jun. 2018

**Community Manager** 

Planned and created the content and copy for social media channels; social media following grew 2300%+ organically in a year.

### Grupo MANTRA® - Ecuador

Jun. 2016 - Nov 2016

**Marketing Department Intern** 

Developed and executed a marketing plan with extensive product testing and validation, resulting in successful negotiations with Walt Disney and sales of over 5000 units in a month to top chains in Ecuador.